[{"answer": "Well, mathematically the number was right, 46.4 percent of the people pay no federal income tax.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Did you agree that when Mitt Romney said that 47 percent of Americans are victims who basically scrounge off the state?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I'd rather be ahead than behind right now.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "What are you guys going to do about this?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not nearly that pessimistic at all.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "So this campaign has got to regroup, refocus and do something pretty sharp, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "I am great.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, I mean, Bob McDonnell, bless his heart for trying his best to put on a still upper lip.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "I mean what is the view from the Democrats' side?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Well, you know, first of all, redistribution, Barack Obama saying that he wants to make sure we have a fair society and we have Mitt Romney who's in favor of obviously redistributing up.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "So what do you have to say to that, Jennifer?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Well, because the trajectory is right.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Not withstanding Mitt Romney's capacity for gaffes, which is clear and present, and causing them problems, if you take the bigger picture, why should any president in America be re-elected when unemployment is over 8 percent?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well, first, let's start with the Guantanamo detainee.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "What do we know about both these things?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, look, there is no question that given -- you know, when I had been in Libya, in Tripoli, and met with Ambassador Stevens, he had acknowledged to me in a long conversation that in fact there was an increase of extremism in eastern Libya.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Where does this leave us in terms of going forward in the investigation?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "You know, it's hard to say.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Do you feel, from all we're now hearing, that he was properly protected or should there have been more done for him there?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, while there is a lot of uncertainty about who exactly killed Ambassador Stevens, there's no doubt that al Qaeda and the Islamic Maghreb, which is the group they're talking about, is something we should be losing a lot of sleep over.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "There was more of that that's much less true of al Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb than others.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Isn't that so the migration was fighting either with al Qaeda or offshoot groups and then wind up moving into Libya?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "There's really not much of a center structure to it anymore.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Or is it a sort of amorphous series of terror cells around the world now?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "I don't -- I mean I think that this goes in kind of a sign.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "You're seeing this kind of ongoing and increasing instability if al Qaeda is still operating with these cells?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Well, that particularly argument is not one that I would have made, to tell you the truth.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "If he was -- if you take out all the rhetoric, if you take out all the gaffe element and the rhetoric, and you cut to his principle point that he claims he's been making a lot on the stump which is that, you know, a lot of people in America, mainly the ones who vote for Barack Obama don't much tax, they don't pay income tax, and are basically living off government handouts?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Well, no, I don't think it is accurate.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Is it -- is it accurate?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I don't remember what the number was precisely.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Was it 10 trillion?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "UDLOW: I want to say a couple of things on this Romney stuff, I think sort of ripped it apart earlier.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What was the counter point you were going to come back?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, the joke has been that he needs to hire a management consultant from Bain to try to rescue his campaign.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "And the reason has to be Mitt Romney, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "RISTOFF: I think that part of it is that he spent six years now effectively in a Republican primary bubble, talking to people where everybody sort of thinks that the 47 percent is this parasitic group in America.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Why is he proving to be right now anyway so haphazard?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Perhaps he just doesn't like those numbers.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Why did he not want to say that, do you think?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "As an old Reagan guy, literally, in the last century, I worked for Reagan in his first term.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "I'm surprised that on all of the statistical information available, only one I think incumbent president in history has been re-elected with unemployment over eight percent, and that was FDR?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "I don't see why it should b.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "On the redistribution thing, what is redistribution and why has it become a dirty word?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Let me push back at the notion that taxes make all the difference in growth.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Final word, Nick?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Um, he got kicked out of the country and --", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "In very simple terms, what happened here with you and your ex-husband?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "He had his visa -- yes exactly, he had his visa revoked.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "He had his visa revoked?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "He is German.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "He is German?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "I went to visit them, yes.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "You went over to France with the children to see him?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Is this indefinitely?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Well, the American judge said this, the California judge.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Therefore the French have decided everyone stays there apart from you?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I'm beside myself.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "How do you feel about this?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "I have long been interested in the rights of children in contested divorce cases.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "How is it possible?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "It's an American judge, a woman, American judge who decided that it would be best for everybody if the children moved out of this country.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "This is an American judge?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "I think they have an idea, but they don't really.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Do they know what is going on?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Three and five.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "How old are they?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Not -- not so much.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Were you amicable at all?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Have you tried to appeal to him and his humanity over this?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "He says no, we are going through the court system.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "What does he say?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Well, I think we have to find a very good established lawyer who emphasizes the rights of children to find the right vehicle, whether it be a federal court lawsuit protecting the interests of the children as American citizens, whether it be an appeal in the California courts.", "docId": "120919pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "What is the next legal step that you can take on Kelly's behalf?", "qSentId": 584}]